The teacher's coming!
You're finally awake.
How are you feeling?
Does your head still hurt?
I'm fine.
Did the teacher come by?
If you're that scared,
then quit smoking.
Are you trying
to kill yourself?
I told him
you didn't smoke.
Thanks.
Don't do it again, okay?
You'll cover for me again
next time, won't you?
Teacher's pet.
You had me worried.
Thanks for worrying
about me.
I hope it's not a bad concussion.
Let's ask the nurse later.
Or maybe go back
to the hospital.
I'll stay with you.
I've gotta get to class.
Come on.
I've told you already.
I don't want
cheesy clichés.
And you threw in
a love triangle.
Oh, please.
Put a bunch of guys
and girls together,
and love triangles
just happen.
My dating show
is all about
what makes people shine.
So what's your thing?
I play piano.
Everyone already
knows that.
Show us
something different.
That's what
people remember.
I cook.
Every guy says
he can cook.
Not exactly unique.
Like what?
Buddha's Temptation,
golden yam ring,
braised pork belly, triple delight
sesame shrimp, salad spring rolls
pumpkin buttermilk shrimp,
scallops with broccoli
and shark fin soup.
Impressive!
Where'd you learn all that?
My dad owns a restaurant.
I've never met a guy
who can cook like that.
Then lunch is on you.
We've got a staff kitchen.
Help yourself.
Please...
Oh, he can actually chop.
Yeah.
He's so hot!
Can I be on the show?
Cole, give me a hand.
Huh?
Sure.
Grab the celery.
Which one's the celery?
This one.
What are you doing?
It's a dating show.
It's not
just about cooking.
I need to work
on my chemistry, too.
Good point.
Maybe we'll get
some good footage!
Hold it by the stem.
Start at an angle.
Then keep slicing.
Look! Cole's blushing.
Thinner.
Got it?
Ouch!
You can't even chop.
How are we shooting this?
Hey, are you always this tough
on the girls?
Are you okay?
Let me help you.
Prawns.
Got it.
Sesame.
Alright.
Cooking wine.
Okay.
Salt...
What are you doing?
Oh.
I looked up
Phil's recipes.
This should be everything.
Just making sure
I didn't miss anything.
I couldn't find
the goji berries.
Sorry. I'll go get them.
It's okay.
We've got enough.
I'll be right back.
You don't need all this.
We can't eat that much.
But it won't taste right.
It's just a practice run.
You don't have to
try so hard.
Okay.
Hi, I'm Jan.
I know.
I'm a content creator.
I was pretty big
seven years ago.
Now...
I'm yesterday's news.
I know.
I'm one of the contestants.
Can we talk?
About what?
Don't people
on these shows
usually have a match?
Why don't we team up?
Older women
are in right now.
We'd make a great pair.
You're just chasing clout.
You're right.
I want the exposure.
That's why
I'm offering a deal.
I've got something
to offer, too.
Don't I?
I know you hate the hype.
Everyone who comes to you
just wants your clout.
I'm different.
I know the right people.
I can introduce you
to real music producers.
Interested?
I can't promise
they'll sign you.
I can only introduce you.
What happens after that
is up to your talent.
So what's the deal?
Wow.
I had this
whole pitch ready.
Didn't think
it'd be that easy.
Smoke?
I don't.
Sorry. No smoking.